

# SEMENCENCO VICTOR

#### FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

I'm a trilingual with a Master Degree in Computer Engineering. I have worked on enterprise projects for companies such as Stellantis using Scrum (obtained the CSPO certification) and SAFe. Experienced in leading teams and effectively communicating and collaborating with both stakeholders and software architects.

+393463667777

victor.semencenco@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/victor-semencenco

### **Hard Skills**

- Angular
- React
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- CSS/SCSS/Bootstrap
- Git

#### **Soft Skills**

- Project Management
- Comunication
- Leadership
- Flexibility
- Teamwork

## Spoken Languages

- English C1
- Italian C2
- Romanian C2
- French A2
- German A2

## Certifications

- Scrum Alliance Certified Scrum Product Owner (CSPO)
- Cambridge ESOL Certification C1 english level assessment

#### **Tools**

- VS Code
- Jira
- Flama/Invision/Zeplin
- Mural

#### Erasmus

• Master of Medialogy - Aalborg University in Copenhagen, Denmark

## **Work Experience**

#### ⊀REPLY Consultant | Xister Reply

Stellantis' PSA Web Portal Jul 2022 - Present

Following the SAFe agile framework, I have led a team of 5 developers and have been responsible for the frontend development of Stellantis' new PSA web portal. Used Jira as project management tool, JavaScript, Typescript and Angular for development, Invision and Zeplin as design tools and Git as version control.

#### Stellantis' FCA Web Portal

Oct 2021 - Jul 2022

Following the Scrum agile framework, I have been part of Stellantis' SWX team and have implemented key features (Appstore, Vehicle Status Widgets) for Stellantis' FCA web portal (Maserati, Fiat, Jeep, etc.) in EMEA, NAFTA and LATAM regions.

#### Oliba Prevention Trainer Portal

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021

I have been in charge of Oliba's frontend development website. The website provides informative articles on non-communicable diseases and how to prevent them. I have used mainly React, Typescript, HTML and SCSS.

#### **Toyota Dealer Portal**

May 2021 - Jul 2021

I have been part of the frontend development for Toyota's Dealer Portal. The portal gives the possibility to manage and edit various information about Toyota's clients.

#### **Education**

#### Master of Computer Engineering

Oct 2018 - Apr 2021

Engineering University of Padua - Italy Grade: 108/110

#### **Bachelor of Information Engineering**

Oct 2013 - Sep 2018

Engineering University of Padua - Italy

## **Projects**

Ó

#### Website - Ancient Musical Instrument

Developed a website for the valorization of an ancient roman musical instrument excavated in Voghenza, Italy. Used JavaScript, JQuery and C#.

#### **Unity Game Development**

Designed and developed a 2D videogame in Unity Game Engine using the C# programming language during my Erasmus period in Denmark.